(What do the secretaries think My Star's usual image is?)
Well...
She has a strong personality.
And...
she swears quite a lot.
she's very wasteful with money...
and expects people to cater to her.
That's what I heard.
Didn't she swear at her own staff on set?
- Isn't it a rumour?
- What?
- It's a rumour, isn't it?
- Is it a rumour?
How come it's a rumour?
There's evidence.
- There's footage.
- Well...
(My Star of the day, who's been surrounded by some harsh rumours)
(Today's My Star, Seo In Young)
(She was a member of Jewellery, one of the biggest girl groups...)
(of the 2000s Korean music scene.)
(Her solo career was also a huge success.)
(My babies)
(She had an almost obsessive love for shoes.)
("Seo In Young Effect: Shoe Sales Surge at Department Stores")
("Shoes Are My Babies. My Heart Races Whenever I See Them")
(She sparked a nationwide craze for "new arrivals" in Korea.)
(However)
(A video of her swearing?)
("Seo In Young's Profanity-Filled Video Sparks Controversy")
("Seo In Young Under Fire Over Her Attitude")
("Seo In Young Caught Talking Behind Someone's Back Again")
(Amid the controversies, she stepped away from the spotlight.)
(10 years later)
(Holy)
(10 years later, she launched a YouTube channel...)
(to turn over a new leaf.)
(New Cinderella Seo In Young)
(Just 6 months after launching her channel,)
(she surpassed 930,000 subscribers.)
(Around 290 million total views)
(She's on a path to redemption.)
(Emotional)
(Seo In Young is turning over a new leaf.)
Are you massaging yourself to reduce the puffiness?
I had liposuction on my arms,
so the tissue under my skin feels lumpy.
(My Star doesn't hide anything.)
I need to massage it.
I had a laser treatment on my face for the Waterbomb Festival.
It takes some time for the results to show,
so my face is still a little swollen right now.
This is my breakfast.
(Simple breakfast)
(But her nails aren't simple.)
I'm good at peeling it, right?
You're really good.
(At 10:25am, the secretaries arrived.)
We're wearing the same fabric.
They're completely different.
Hey, the fabrics are similar.
They're not even close.
- Hello.
- Thank you for coming.
- No problem.
I'm Lee Woo Sung. I've been working with In Young.
Nice to meet you.
- Here's the handover file.
- Okay.
- Gosh.
- Take a look.
(What's on My Star's schedule today?)
(My Star's Schedule: 1pm, Arrival, hair and makeup)
Today,
she has a lingerie photoshoot.
(A lingerie photoshoot?)
She has a lingerie photoshoot.
A lingerie photoshoot?
- Yes. It's a lingerie photoshoot?
- A lingerie photoshoot?
My goodness.
It'd be uncomfortable.
(He doesn't know where to look.)
(His dimples show as he awkwardly looks around.)
And you should monitor...
her lingerie photoshoot.
Yes. You must monitor her photoshoot.
- That's...
- Is it a good thing or a bad thing?
your job.
And...
(Why is he hesitating?)
- May I continue?
- Sure.
- You look quite nervous.
- No.
- Okay.
- I'm just reading it.
There's a manual for dealing with In Young.
- That's what I'm reading.
- Yes.
Let me talk about that.
When she first meets you,
she'll try...
to establish dominance by staring at you.
Why? Does she always do that?
Yes. She tends to test where she stands with someone...
through staring contests.
So I'd advise you not to avoid eye contact with her.
If you lose the staring contest,
you're in for a rough day.
Why are you worried?
- What?
- Didn't she turn over a new leaf?
- I think she became even worse.
- She's still turning it.
She's still turning over a new leaf.
- She's not done yet?
- No.
Suddenly, my molar started hurting.
Claiming dominance.
- I use my eyes.
- How?
Hello.
(A piercing stare)
I never break eye contact.
I'll welcome them with a smile, though.
(She needs to practice smiling as well.)
(She's ready to claim dominance.)
She's been on a diet...
for about a month.
- Yes.
- So she's become very sensitive.
(1. Win the staring contest 2. Be mindful of her temper)
- Seo Jin is good...
- Probably...
- at handling it.
- Me?
- It won't be easy.
- Okay.
She's quite fickle.
You should treat her like a baby.
Don't think of her as a woman.
Think of her as a five-year-old boy.
You'd better compliment her when she's doing well.
It'll make your job easier.
But she's not a baby.
She's not.
- She's in her 40s.
- Yes.
(That's true, but...)
No matter what, I can't treat her like a five-year-old boy.
And I hate five-year-old boys.
I hate little boys.
(He knows exactly what he doesn't like.)
When she works with her managers, she acts like a newborn baby.
She whines a lot...
and changes her mind all the time.
She has some personality issues.
- She doesn't have issues.
- She does.
- She doesn't.
- That's why...
there were a lot of controversies.
- It's all in the past.
- Am I wrong?
- People don't change.
She's turning over a new leaf.
I'm telling you. People don't change.
There are three phrases...
- she often says.
- What are they?
"I'm not doing it."
"I don't want to do it."
"I'm not eating that."
I say those things a lot.
She's just like you.
- "I'm not doing it."
- "I don't want to do it."
- I say that a lot.
- You guys are the same.
- Yes.
- Does she swear?
- No. She never swears at us.
- She doesn't?
- She isn't like that.
- Has she stopped doing that?
Yes.
When she's feeling a little worn out,
call her "Princess." It'll cheer her up.
I'll treat her like My Lady today.
- No. Call her Princess.
- Not My Lady? Just Princess?
- Princess.
- Princess. That's it.
- Okay.
And...
this is the bag I prepared for her schedule.
There are a few things she needs today.
This is lip gloss.
I heard she didn't like using lip gloss.
She hates it.
For today's photoshoot,
she needs this powder pact,
- and most importantly, - What's that?
a nail brush.
(Lip gloss, powder pact, and nail brush?)
- A nail brush.
- What? Nail?
- Her nails are very long.
- Yes.
Yes.
These are a bit different.
I didn't use dark colours because it's a lingerie photoshoot.
(They're called witch nails.)
(Starting to get annoyed)
It's to keep her nails clean.
- And that's our job?
- Yes.
She'll show her hand like this later.
What does she do on her own?
- These are only for the photoshoot.
- What?
And this is the most important.
During the photoshoot,
she becomes...
professional.
Make a note of things...
she needs to improve, such as, "That expression isn't good."
"That pose doesn't look good."
So I'd advise you not to avoid eye contact with her.
(Manual for dealing with My Star)
(It's a lingerie photoshoot day.)
(She's on an emotional roller coaster because she's on a diet.)
(Don't lose the staring contest.)
(Treat her like a newborn baby.)
(What she hates most is putting on lip gloss.)
(Reapply lip gloss to her regularly.)
(Take notes while monitoring the photoshoot.)
You should be in charge today. I can't do this.
I can't do it either.
- You can't leave.
- I can't do this.
- No.
- Please don't go.
- I mean...
- I can't do this.
- the handover...
- This is...
- took 15 minutes.
- No.
- I...
- Hey.
She isn't turning over a new leaf at all.
There are still a lot more left.
- There are still a lot more left?
- There are still a lot more left.
I can't do this.
Turning over a new leaf?
- This is impossible.
- I enjoyed her YouTube videos.
We'll be back next year.
- Please.
- Take it back.
- You can see something like this...
- I don't think we can do it.
at the end of her videos.
Okay. Then...
This is a company card.
(The company card is here.)
(Okay. The deal is done.)
Secretary Seo Jin!
Secretary Lee Seo Jin!
Why does she keep calling me?
No. Seo Jin, you put the lip gloss on me.
(The secretaries do My Star's makeup for the first time.)
Here comes the princess!
Here she comes.
It's hard to call her a princess when she's only wearing lingerie.
Is she dressed appropriately for TV?
You should give me a straw.
Oh, right. Okay.
(And...)
My mother passed away...
- four years ago.
- I see.
(My Star's heartfelt story as she opens up to the secretaries)
That's when I thought about how great it'd be to have a husband.
My first marriage didn't work out,
but I have a boyfriend now.
I want a happy married life this time.
How can we make our marriage last?
Overcome with joint prayers or something.
(They're finally meeting My Star.)
Let's just let it go.
Thank you for coming today.
How long have you been working with her?
- It's been around nine years.
- That's a long time.
- Gosh.
- Is it hard to work as a manager?
No, it's so easy.
But I'm so happy that you came today.
I see.
Has she been living here for a long time?
No. It's been around two years.
- It hasn't been that long.
- Yes.
After getting a divorce?
- Okay.
Yes.
- I'll get going then.
- Okay.
- Bye. I'll keep that in mind.
- Good luck.
Good luck.
(They arrive in front of her apartment.)
What's this?
(He rang the doorbell.)
(My Star claims dominance by staring.)
Who is it?
(Their first encounter will make or break the day.)
Oh, my. Hello!
(Just as they were warned, she starts a staring contest.)
Your hair is still...
- Why?
- Hello.
Come on in.
(Eye contact)
(He breaks the ice without letting her intimidate him.)
Why?
- The last time I saw you, - Come on in.
- your hair was platinum blond.
- Hello.
- What did you say?
- The last time I saw you,
your hair was platinum blond.
- In the past?
- In the past.
- Come in.
- Okay.
- Well...
- Your hair is still...
- Hello.
- Come on in.
- Hello!
(He greets her a little more politely this time.)
(She didn't hear him.)
(Scratching)
(I feel like my position might be slipping.)
You have so many shoes.
Oh, my.
- You still have a lot of shoes.
- No.
- My gosh.
(The shoe rack is full.)
(Dozens of boots)
- I'd love to give you some.
- You have so many boots.
- Are those all yours?
- It's nice to meet you.
We haven't met properly before.
We bumped into each other at an event.
Yes. It was an event.
- At an event. Yes.
- And a gathering with older people.
- Your hair was platinum blond.
- Yes.
(She also greets Kwang Kyu warmly.)
- Your hair was platinum blond.
- Yes. Hi, Kwang Kyu.
It's been a long time.
I heard he had contacted you this morning.
- He sent you a message.
- A message?
Well...
"I'm looking forward to working with you, My Star."
I blocked you.
Why?
I thought a random person messaged me.
- We exchanged numbers before.
- Well...
- Seven years ago.
- Did we?
We met in Yeouido.
We did?
My goodness.
I feel miserable.
I shouldn't have said that.
Why?
Take a seat.
You can sit here.
- Give us a house tour.
- You can sit here.
- A house tour.
- A house tour?
- There's nothing to see.
- There's nothing to see?
I've never been here before.
- Sure.
- Yes.
- If that's what you want.
- Just a simple house tour.
What do you want?
- I'll explain. This is the kitchen.
- I...
I'm a subscriber.
- You are?
- Yes. I'm a subscriber.
How about you?
You...
You're obviously not.
- "New Cinderella..."
- No one...
(He got on her nerves right from the start.)
- "New Cinderella..."
- No one... I subscribe to no one.
I don't subscribe to anyone.
- But you should subscribe to me.
- I will. I'll subscribe today.
No. Right now.
- Now? I didn't bring my phone.
- Now.
- You didn't? I'll check later then.
- No.
- Okay.
- Okay?
(He managed to calm her down.)
This is the walk-in closet.
You can go in. It's my walk-in closet.
- What?
- Why do you have so many clothes?
You didn't turn over a new leaf!
You are still the same!
- Why?
- You have too many clothes.
(Spotting piles of clothes)
No. I turned over a new leaf.
- You did?
- Yes. It's well-organised.
I heard she turned over a new leaf.
I expected her walk-in closet to be empty.
I thought it'd be empty.
But there were still piles of clothes.
(It's about to burst.)
There's barely any room to walk in the entryway.
She still has a long way to go.
(Is My Star still as materialistic as ever?)
What do you want to know about?
I'm just looking around.
- Okay.
- This is a library.
- Yes. This is a library.
- I saw it.
Do you use the computer at the desk?
No, I don't.
- But I got a desktop.
- For decoration?
Massage chairs.
What are those wine bottles doing here?
- Wine.
- Is there wine in those bottles?
There's wine in them.
(The wine that starts her morning)
It seems you never tidy up your house.
No, I tidied it up.
- You did?
- I did.
- I tidied it up.
- This is how it looks after that?
- Yes.
- I see.
Why do you have so many massage chairs?
For massage.
She loves getting massages.
- Yes. I love it.
- She does?
- She massages herself all day.
- I like massage devices.
- Massage devices.
- Yes.
- Massage...
- Don't you have to get massages...
- I did.
- after liposuction?
I'm massaging myself.
Your arms look so much slimmer now.
Totally. I can tell the fat is gone from here.
Doesn't it hurt?
It's crazy.
Your arms look slimmer, but your face is still quite chubby.
What? What did you say?
(What? What did you say?)
- I mean...
- Why?
The fat on my face hasn't gone down yet!
Not yet.
Did you get liposuction on your face too?
No, I didn't. I got a laser treatment.
This is the living room. And this is my dog.
- Yes.
- Can we see your bedroom?
My bedroom? It's just dirty.
(Macaroon, 14 years old, female)
Okay. Seo Jin.
Can you do this for me?
- What is it?
- I want to take it with me.
- I have a photoshoot today.
- Yes.
If I eat something on set...
Do you want me to take it with me?
Be quiet.
- Come here.
- Why is she barking at you so much?
- Why is she barking only at me?
- Oh, my. Come here.
- After our eyes met...
- She's never seen a hairless man.
After our eyes met,
she started barking so much.
(Barking)
What's wrong with you, Macaroon? Why are you so aggressive?
- Why is she barking only at me?
- Why are you so aggressive?
- She's never seen a hairless man.
- Stop barking.
Stop.
(Kwang Kyu even got out-dominated by the dog.)
She was used to seeing people with blond hair.
- She's never seen someone bald.
- Stop barking.
Sit down.
Take a seat.
(Today's pecking order: In Young, Seo Jin, Maracoon, Kwang Kyu)
I heard you have a lingerie photoshoot today.
- Yes. It's a lingerie photoshoot.
- Yes?
I haven't eaten since yesterday.
- How revealing is it?
- You must be sensitive then.
It's just lingerie.
- Panties and bras.
- Just lingerie?
- Just panties and bras?
- Yes.
- Today?
- Are you excited?
- It's quite intense.
- Are you okay with that?
- Yes.
It doesn't matter to us.
But the thing is...
I made the lingerie myself.
- You did?
- Yes.
- I made it.
- Are you running a business?
Yes.
- It's a collaboration.
- So you're...
expanding.
I need to strike while the iron is hot!
Come on.
I envy you.
- You've started expanding.
- I need to strike.
(My Star runs a lingerie business now.)
- I want you to do this for me.
- Okay.
- Like which one... You know...
- During a lingerie photoshoot...
- So...
- a lot about women.
I'm too...
- old now.
- It seems you're taking a break.
- I'm too old now.
- But you'd still have an opinion...
on which one looks better.
Do you have preferences too, Kwang Kyu?
Do you have any preferences when it comes to women's lingerie?
(My Star asked about their lingerie preferences.)
I like simple ones.
- Simple?
- Yes.
- That's my preference.
- Like seamless?
Seamless. Yes.
Like nude bras?
Something like that.
I feel like you'd like pink bras.
- With laces and stuff?
- Yes. With laces.
I like laces.
(He likes pink and laces.)
Like Vivien.
Vivien?
Still?
You still have a lot of dreams.
(What does women's lingerie mean to you?)
I remember my mom's.
Whenever I went to my mom's house,
there were always her saggy panties hanging out on the veranda.
It was definitely a brief, but it looked more like boyshorts.
(Briefs that looked like something in between briefs and boyshorts)
Seeing that broke my heart.
I hope she stays healthy.
(Kwang Kyu, a devoted son with big dreams)
Why have you been so quiet recently?
It seems you don't want to date anymore.
No, I don't.
- Why?
- I'm too old for that.
I'm in my mid-50s.
Don't you want to have kids?
I'm in my mid-50s. I'm too old to raise kids.
(Do you think so?)
I heard...
you were irresistible to women.
Apparently, they just can't get enough of you.
I heard that the celebrities who broke up with you were devastated.
(My Star mentions the rumours that he's a bad boy.)
- Who said that?
- "What's wrong with him?"
(Lee Seo Jin? What's wrong with him?)
"What makes him so irresistible?"
I would always say this.
"What kind of person is he?"
I've met all kinds of men.
So Seo Jin is the only man you've never dated.
Right.
But he was in one relationship after another.
- So was I.
- So was you.
Right.
We didn't even have any way of crossing paths.
Was I supposed to do a cellphone commercial or something?
(The final boss who could finally win him over has appeared.)
- Let's do it today.
- I wish I did.
Let's do it today.
(It seems My Star claimed the top spot.)
You have something in common.
You both have dimples in pretty much the same spot.
- You have 1 here. I have 2 here.
- The thing...
with people with dimples is...
What now?
You can't get anything too intense when you have skin treatments.
Or your dimples disappear.
That's why I can't do anything here.
- You can't.
- Is that so?
That's why you didn't lose much fat from your face...
- even after the treatment.
- Yes.
- You're right.
- That's why it's still chubby.
(Glaring)
- What I mean is, you look healthy.
- You're so annoying.
You look healthy.
(The 2nd-in-command secretary gets on her nerves.)
I have no energy because I haven't eaten anything.
Your face is chubby, which is nice.
What do you mean, my face is chubby?
- Your face...
- You're getting on my nerves.
- I mean...
You lost a lot of weight, but your face...
My face just doesn't seem to lose fat.
I told you. Your face is still chubby.
- My face...
- Your face is chubby.
- Only your arms are slim.
- You're so annoying.
That doesn't look normal.
Only your arms are slim.
You look like E.T.
Are you kidding me?
(Exploding)
What are you talking about?
Do I look that bad?
- Only your arms are slim.
- Do I look that bad?
No. Your face looks perfectly healthy.
It's just that your arms look too slim.
- Come on.
- Compared to your arms...
- Hey.
- What?
Tell her that she looks pretty.
What I'm saying is, she looks healthy and good.
Seo Jin!
- I mean...
- Mr. Secretary!
(Startled)
(Seo Jin!)
(Mr. Secretary!)
I mean, I like that you look healthy.
You can edit the photos anyway.
To make your face look slimmer.
Only your arms look slim, though.
So you're saying I look weird!
You look healthy.
You look healthy and great.
(Shivering)
(Shaking his head)
Her voice is way too high-pitched.
She sounds like...
she's freaking out.
Mr. Secretary!
(It's so fun to tease her.)
I didn't know your voice was this high.
(Her voice is too loud for someone who is turning over a new leaf.)
You always had a high singing voice.
- Yes. I sing in a high register.
- You sing in a high register.
- That'd make you a good singer.
- Yes.
She's great.
She's rather underestimated.
- I'm quite good.
- Usually...
She was known more for dancing than singing,
so her vocal talent was often overlooked.
Right. You won "Immortal Songs" too.
(These two are no pushovers.)
I brought him.
- Well...
- Have you eaten?
- No, I haven't. What's this?
- You haven't?
"In Young Mushroom?" What's this?
- Is there a snack like this?
- My fan...
- No. My fan made it.
- Your fan made it?
(Her fan made the snack for her.)
I have an amazing fan like that.
I thought it was an actual snack.
I heard you were really popular these days,
but was it this much?
(I heard you're really popular these days, but was it this much?)
Seo Jin, I used to be popular...
when you saw me back in the day.
- You were more popular then.
- Right.
You were popular then,
but your popularity went down.
(But it went down.)
Your popularity went down.
That's right. I took a long break.
- That's right. With all the issues.
- Yes.
- But now...
- You're back up now.
Yes. I'm back.
(Having her in the palm of his hand)
It's the era where people like Seo In Young are back in style.
(Listen to him talk.)
Let's check your qualities as a manager here.
Why do you think my style works now?
(My Star asked a difficult question.)
You should go first.
- Why?
- I...
I haven't even watched them.
- You watched her videos.
- I mean...
you'd know...
- that I'm popular these days.
- That's right.
Why do you think I'm popular?
Why?
- I'm sorry.
- What is that?
What is that sound? You're working.
- I'm...
- You're working.
- Come on!
- I just...
There's always someone like that even in church.
- Put it on vibrate. You're working.
- On vibrate.
That's your charm.
- You're working.
- That's your charm.
(What is he talking about?)
Someone who doesn't look like she would go to church...
goes to church.
- Right? I think that's a charm.
- I...
saw her wear the choir robe...
- Right.
- and sing.
That was so funny.
It really didn't suit her.
She looks like...
she'd spit on people at church.
But she was there singing.
That's a contrasting charm.
- That's funny.
- That's the charm.
That's funny.
- A contrasting charm?
- Yes.
- You have that.
- What else?
That's the first one.
This is how the redemption story works.
I honestly...
used to swear a lot.
But I'll atone for it now...
- Yes.
- while going to church.
I'll pray...
and become a new person.
That's what people like.
It's an era of forgiving.
Those who haven't forgiven me still haven't forgiven me.
You can't expect everyone to do so.
- More than half is enough.
- Right.
That would be enough.
- That's what you think.
- Yes. That's what I think.
Fifty percent.
(The secretary who controls My Star's mood)
There's something I prepared for you.
First of all,
you have to listen.
I think managers are characters...
who represent me wherever they go.
So I don't like anything that's tacky.
You have to dress according to the time and occasion.
I'd like you...
to get changed into clothes that are my style.
- I prepared these gifts.
- Really?
Yes.
(The uniforms My Star actually prepared)
(Wig, hoodie, pants)
(My Star's favourite hip-hop style)
Look. Hip-hop.
- Look. Hip-hop.
- This...
- Isn't this worse?
- No. Yours is worse.
Do you know what this is?
This is an outfit you wear...
when you're meeting someone for the third time on a blind date.
- Really?
- Yes.
- What about this?
- This...
- What's with the wig?
- We have to wear wigs?
- Today...
Of course.
Try it on and then talk.
That's your hairstyle.
Why are you using your hairstyle?
- Seo Jin.
- You want us to look the same.
- You came to represent me today.
- Yes.
- You'll do it anyway...
- Did you hurt your finger?
Yesterday...
(An unexpected sweet concern)
(He's worried about My Star's hand before the photo shoot.)
Yesterday, I cut it while cutting some peaches.
You said you were on a diet. You're taking lots of sugar.
I also...
I also ate jjamppong and all.
- All right.
- There's a changing room there.
- Where?
- Here.
It's going to be hot in these.
It's so hot.
(Genie will wear anything for My Star.)
Ta-da!
It's hot.
(A hip-hop duo in their 50s)
You look so cool!
It's nice but hot.
It's for summer.
- It's for summer.
- But it's so thick.
You have to close that.
Don't keep it open. You look like an old man.
You look so nice.
It's hot. It's fine, but...
You should endure that for the fashion.
Come here.
(It's time to wear the bowl cut wig.)
Your head...
(He willingly lowers his head.)
- Is this how you wear it?
- Yes. You wear it like this.
(Exclaiming)
- Do we look like siblings?
- It's really... Yes.
We look like siblings. Look.
Look.
He looks good. What's happening?
(The sibling with dimples from the US)
(He's not so sure.)
Is it because it's your hairstyle?
It looks cool. Come here.
Kwang Kyu.
(It's Kwang Kyu's turn.)
I can't wear wigs because my head gets hot.
No.
No...
- I get sweaty easily.
- Let me just see.
Look.
This is hip-hop!
(The big sister, Hip Kwang Kyu)
This is like Seo In Young and Boys.
Look!
This is amazing.
(Happy)
This is what it looks like.
(He doesn't really hate having hair after a while.)
I'll lower the temperature setting.
You look good. I was trying to make things funny,
but why do they look good?
We'll wear them later. It's so hot right now.
- I should pull my pants up a bit.
- No, keep them down.
No.
Don't pull them up.
You should keep it sagging like hip-hop.
These days, you just wear them low on your hips.
- But they'll get dragged.
- Right.
That's right.
Right.
My mom will scold me.
No. Keep them like that.
- Okay.
I should do as the princess says.
- Princess.
Princess!
(The magic word that makes her happy, "Princess")
She likes it.
Princess. Gosh.
I heard...
you were not on a diet for today's shoot.
- It's for the Waterbomb Festival.
- No.
- Starting today...
- For today's shoot?
until the Waterbomb Festival.
I'll have to starve for a few days.
When is the Waterbomb Festival?
It's on the 22nd.
- The Waterbomb Festival.
- Take him with you to Sokcho.
Right.
I have something else that day.
You have a shooting?
- Really?
- We...
We're working with RESCENE that day.
- Is it that day?
- Yes.
- It's on that day.
- They're hot these days.
We only work with the hottest people.
Really?
(We only work with the hottest people.)
(Happy)
(My Star's shoulders go up with his fine line.)
Princess.
I feel great!
(Her energy...)
Bring it up!
(is out of control.)
(Kwang Kyu can't handle My Star's energy.)
I'm so happy.
There's a lot to take.
And these. Hold on.
I have to spray this.
- I care about the scent.
- Sure.
(They must spray some deodorizer before going out.)
You have to have a scent.
- It smells like the hotel.
- Right?
- Yes.
- Right.
It's a luxurious scent.
I love this scent.
(My Star's scent is the secretaries' scent.)
(The luxurious scent brings up her energy as well.)
It's such a luxurious scent.
It's good to spray on clothes you care about.
It's black label.
It's a luxurious scent, so it lasts long.
It takes 52 minutes.
(12pm, heading to the lingerie photo shoot)
How did you happen to start your channel?
Is it easier to make your channel than appearing on shows?
What I liked about YouTube...
is that I could be really honest.
I really want...
to show people everything I am...
to the point that they wonder,
"How far will she go?"
(She suddenly appeared on the YouTube world.)
(Revealing her bare face)
(Opening her unfiltered daily life)
(I had five nose surgeries.)
(Opening up about her plastic surgery...)
(in detail)
(Opening up about her liposuction)
(Opening up about her divorce)
(I've never taken a break from dating.)
(Opening up about her new boyfriend)
(Revealing her stepmom and dad for the first time)
Honestly speaking,
I take medication for panic disorder and depression.
(She even opened up about her pain and flaws.)
Let's enjoy my life...
together!
(My Star, the ultimate in honesty)
I thought I'd just let people know...
that I'm alive.
I didn't know, but people told me that my channel was a hit.
"What?"
"Your videos have more than two million views."
"So?"
- Two million.
- I didn't know that.
(Every time she uploaded a video, it got record-breaking views.)
I think I did a good job to come back through my channel.
It became a way to communicate.
(The joy of connecting with her fans after so long)
I can read the comments right away.
Of course, there are haters,
but there were so many supportive comments.
It was nice.
Did you meet your new boyfriend...
while doing New Cinderella Seo In Young?
No, I met him before that.
Before starting New Cinderella Seo In Young?
It was before.
Actually,
I have panic disorder,
- and...
- Panic disorder?
I had severe depression.
So I couldn't work.
I couldn't be on shows because I was so afraid.
I had it for ten years.
I couldn't even listen to music...
because I was depressed.
Then...
I even got divorced.
I thought, "What should I do now?"
(After getting divorced, I thought, "What should I do now?")
"What should I do?"
I thought I couldn't work again,
but my current boyfriend...
kept telling me I could do it.
- Then...
- I'm glad you met him.
Yes. Then...
I thought I'd just start with my channel.
You did a good job.
It's doing well in the end.
That's right. But I didn't think it would do so well.
Right.
(My Star is very honest.)
(Before they knew it, they arrived in Seoul.)
(Glancing)
If My Star didn't buy shoes and bags...
- Right. I'd own a building here.
- You'd have...
You'd own a building.
My dad did the math, and he said I'd have had three buildings.
- Really?
- We have the records.
My dad likes keeping records.
- He keeps a budget?
- Yes.
- He must be frugal.
- Totally.
So to him, I was crazy.
I spent tens of thousands of dollars on liposuction,
and he took my card.
So now, he gives me an allowance of 1,000 dollars.
(My Star is living on an allowance.)
- A month?
- You would have your own card.
I don't.
He cut them all.
How do you live on 1,000 dollars a month?
He called all the card companies.
- He was with me.
- How do you live on that?
I just buy food.
I cook.
You wouldn't eat so much.
Right. I don't eat so much these days.
- I have a question as a subscriber.
- Yes.
Why do you blur your father?
Dad doesn't want his face to be revealed.
(My Star's father values his privacy.)
(I already gave her the inheritance.)
(When?)
(I gave her faith.)
(He passed down his faith.)
(My Star's father is a church elder.)
His voice is really nice.
- My father...
- He seems very caring.
really values his privacy.
But he prays in front of people at church.
That's why I think that's a contradiction.
(My Star doesn't hold back, even about her dad.)
- He's so charming.
- Everyone knows his face...
- at church.
- Yes.
I don't know why he wants his face covered on YouTube.
He's full of contradictions.
I feel very uncomfortable as a subscriber.
- That's true.
- Yes.
My dad loves watching My Genie Secretary.
- He'll listen to you.
- You should tell him.
I'd appreciate it if you could reveal your face a little.
Thank you.
(By subscriber Kwang Kyu)
The studio. We're here.
(1pm, arriving at the lingerie photo shoot)
I'm done with parking.
(1pm, lingerie photo shoot studio, hair and make up)
I'll get in first.
(The studio is busy before the photo shoot.)
Hello.
There are so many tasty snacks.
(The snacks capture My Star's eyes.)
But I can't have it.
Hello.
Please take care of me well.
- Yes. Go ahead and eat.
- Okay.
(Glancing)
Are you here?
Come and set up our things, secretaries.
(Coming, Princess.)
Where are you going?
Kwang Kyu is gone. Where did he go?
(The door shuts.)
(Leaving)
He's just leaving me behind.
Hello.
(The secretaries are here.)
- Hello.
Hello.
(They get ready to take care of her at the photo shoot.)
Look at this.
How can they prepare so many tasty snacks?
I've been starving for about two days...
for the lingerie photo shoot.
I only had vegetables.
I didn't even have eggs because it might give me a belly.
I was on a diet for a month. I lost about 4kg.
(Feeling envious)
I've never lost so much weight.
(The most serious diet of My Star's life)
I can't eat.
- What?
- What are you going to do?
If you're to work hard, you have to eat.
Go ahead and eat.
We'll starve with you.
- Really?
- With My Star...
There's some salad as well.
There are fruits as well.
Aren't you going to eat?
There are so many things to eat.
Since My Star can't eat,
we shouldn't eat as well.
No.
Have some fruits at least.
You have to eat to work hard later.
What?
(The packed lunch remained out of reach.)
Should we get the shoes out?
What? Should we get them out?
(My Star's photo shoot prep is a priority.)
(Carrying)
This place...
- Right. That...
- Hello.
(Everyone's busy preparing for My Star's photo shoot.)
(He gets the timetable for the shoot.)
The agenda is packed.
(Lingerie brand photo shoot schedule)
(The lingerie photo shoot will feature 6 different outfits.)
There are only six outfits.
(He takes the gown she'll wear between the looks.)
Should I take the gown?
I think we'll have to keep it and put it on her.
Will you put it on her in between the shoots?
You should do that.
(Seo Genie will be in charge of the gown.)
(He starts organising the shoes after getting the gown.)
(Walkers)
(High heels)
(Boots)
(Boots again)
(High heels again)
(The setup for My Star's lingerie photo shoot is ready.)
Those would be around 15cm.
They would be around 20cm.
(20cm killer heels)
It's really 20cm.
It would be higher than 20cm.
I'd be taller than 180cm in those.
You wouldn't be able to walk even 10m in those.
Women are amazing.
(My Star even dances wearing killer heels.)
Why are there so many snacks?
(Kwang Kyu found the snacks.)
Aren't you going to have some?
Aren't you?
(He tests him casually.)
(Seo Genie gets packed lunch.)
(Licking his lips)
Goodness.
(It looks amazing.)
- It looks amazing.
- It looks good.
Nice.
Are you really not going to eat?
(He quickly declared that he'll fast with My Star.)
Are you going to eat?
I never said I'll go hungry.
I'm running low on blood sugar. Should I have some fruits?
(He tries to keep his conscience clear by taking a bite.)
(That's sweet.)
Kwang Kyu... Secretary, what happened?
- No...
- Secretary Kwang Kyu.
(Getting up)
- I'm just eating fruits.
- Fruits.
Just the fruits.
Why are there so many?
(Securing his bite)
(He's trying hard.)
Let's go try it on.
Okay.
Should I try your favourite?
(Seo Genie, the catfish of the packed lunch, tempts him.)
No, no.
You said you wouldn't eat to help My Star.
I mean...
While she gets changed...
What tastes the best?
- What?
- What tastes the best?
Crunchy fried chicken.
(A self-cheat day, while trying not to get caught)
Just eat everything.
There's a mark on my stomach.
(My Star comes out after changing.)
What?
What is this?
(Trembling)
Who is this food for?
(He shouldn't have said he wasn't going to eat.)
(He got caught red handed, with no excuses to make.)
(Someone came to My Star's waiting room.)
Hello.
I'm the brand representative you're shooting today.
You're here. You lost more weight.
- Our lingerie is finally out.
- Exactly.
- I've been wearing it.
- Really?
It's really comfortable.
(This is my time!)
(A brand representative visits to brief her on the outfits.)
- In Young.
- Yes.
- For the briefs...
You wanted your legs to look longer,
- so we adjusted the line.
- Okay.
You also wanted the lining...
to have a higher quality.
Right.
(He makes sure the robe is closed.)
We changed it to a silk-modal blend.
Okay.
Only our brand uses the silk-modal blend.
- That's right.
- Okay.
Right. Then the price...
(The CEO is also worried.)
Right. But it has to be affordable.
That's right.
We incorporated...
- your ideas.
- We incorporated them.
We were able to make the new products.
They're my new product babies.
What do you think?
(My Star's hot new arrivals)
- They're nice.
You don't sound like you mean it.
You like lace lingerie.
Do you have lace?
We have lace lingerie.
(A chic and simple lace lingerie)
- It's cut really low.
- You can't call it lace.
Goodness.
- It's cut really low.
- You can't call it lace.
They're nice.
(I like lace.)
- Let's get ready quickly.
- Okay.
(Getting ready for the shoot)
I need my contacts.
Can you get her contacts?
(How is she going to put on the contacts with those long nails?)
(Grabbing the contacts with her long nails)
(Opening her eyes as wide as she can)
(Putting on the contacts easily even with long nails)
(Checking the colour)
This and...
(Trying on two kinds before making her decision)
I should ask which one is better.
(Putting on a different colour on the other eye)
Which contact is better?
That's Seo Jin's job.
- Really?
- Yes.
(A question while the contact expert is gone)
Seo Jin!
Where did he go?
(Seo Genie is throwing out the lunch.)
(Seo Jin!)
- Where did he go?
- What?
Seo Jin.
Yes?
(Seo Jin is coming.)
Seo Jin. Her contacts.
- Contacts...
- My contacts.
He's also good at putting on contacts.
(Appealing)
Really? I should've asked him.
- Which one's better?
- The contacts?
What's better? Right or left?
(Let me see.)
(Scanning carefully)
(After thinking carefully...)
- It's for the photo shoot.
- Yes.
This one? Yes?
But I like the left one better.
You think so?
Ask the experts.
No, you should know.
(Tilting her head)
Because it shows that you're wearing contacts.
You think so?
But doesn't this side look bigger?
- Because your eye looks bigger?
- Yes.
This side of your eye is bigger.
No, this side is bigger.
No.
Isn't this side better?
- No?
- In Young is gullible.
I'm gullible.
This side?
(Seo Jin's choice)
- The right side looks pretty.
- Okay. The right side it is.
I'll take your word for it.
(I'll trust your choice, Seo Jin.)
(Serving the contacts with his firm opinion)
- Do you want to sit down?
- Let me grab some tissues.
(Preparing tissues just in case)
- It looks warm...
- I need to get the contact out.
Lee Seo Jin!
(Calling the contact expert)
(Lee Seo Jin!)
Why does she keep calling me?
(Let me grab the tissue first.)
My nails...
(Kwang Kyu was eating quietly.)
If I take the contact out now, I'll hurt myself.
Lee Seo Jin!
(Calling Seo Jin anxiously)
- What's wrong?
- Can you remove the contact?
(Seo Genie arrives promptly.)
Take this contact out.
Sit down first.
We can't do it standing up.
No?
Sit down first.
(Calm)
I can't take it out because of my nails.
(The examples of calm person and anxious person)
(Cleaning his hands first)
- Kwang Kyu.
- Yes?
Can you widen her eyes?
What?
Give me one wipe too.
Okay.
(Seo Genie is more careful than anyone else.)
One person will widen the eye while the other person takes it out.
(Jobs distributed)
I'm scared.
Am I widening her eyes?
Yes. Are you going to take it out?
No.
(Kwang Kyu is also scared.)
(Seo Genie will remove the contact if that's what My Star wants.)
Widen her eyes.
(In charge of widening her eye)
Open your eye wide.
(In charge of removing the contact)
(1st attempt failed)
(2nd attempt failed)
(He successfully removes the contact after 3 tries.)
Thank you.
(Grabbing the contact with her long fingernails)
(Putting on the one Seo Jin picked)
(Wear noticeable contacts for a photo shoot.)
(Transforming for the photo shoot)
(Down to the last detail)
(Ready for the photo shoot)
Let's go. It's time to go.
What?
(We should...)
(go too.)
No, you should have to go.
I'll take the robe.
(Taking the robe)
(Stopping)
- Why don't you put it on?
- Me?
(Using the older bestie as his hanger)
(Taking the lead for My Star)
(Entering the studio for the underwear photo shoot)
- Hello.
He's my secretary.
(Shy)
(Her first outfit is cool minimalism.)
(My Star gets ready for the shoot.)
(Grumpy Secretary is watching nervously.)
Let's test first.
(The camera test begins.)
(Trying different poses)
Do you see it?
(From a child...)
She looks like a pro for the photo shoot.
Good.
I love it.
Be bold.
(Already getting approvals during the test)
Very nice. Incredible.
That's perfect.
(My Star is calm when she's working.)
That was cool. She was professional.
It's not easy even for men...
to be only in underwear.
Appearing only in underwear...
means she's a pro.
I respect that.
(Exclaiming at My Star's professional moment)
(My Star becomes calm as soon as she starts working.)
(Grumpy Secretary is monitoring seriously.)
Should I remove the bandage on her finger?
If she's okay with that.
She's okay.
If it's okay,
- can we fix something?
- Yes.
(It turns out she was shooting with a bandage on.)
- Can we fix something?
- Yes.
- A bandage?
(Seo Jin steps forward.)
Oh, no. I forgot to take it off.
Is it okay to remove it though?
It's okay.
(The shoot stops for a second.)
I bumped into something.
Thank you.
(Kwang Kyu appears with a wig on.)
You're wearing it.
(My Star is smiling at Kwang Kyu's wig.)
To cheer you up.
To make My Star cheer up.
For My Star...
(To cheer up my tired Star)
Really?
- Ready?
- What? Yes.
(He's willing to do anything.)
- This is very tight. One, two.
- Okay.
(A man's makeover requires pain and patience.)
It's a bit too tight.
Does it have to be this tight?
Yes, otherwise it comes off.
(The magic is on.)
- It looks good on you.
- Yes?
- You look handsome.
- Thank you.
(My Star is also smiling.)
(Kwang Kyu makes the whole studio smile.)
I put it on to cheer her up. Was it a good idea?
Good job.
(Very good, Kwang Kyu.)
You should do it more often.
(I'd do anything for My Star.)
Kwang Kyu, I appreciate it,
and don't forget to write down feedback for me.
- Do I need to take pictures too?
- What?
- Pictures...
- That's not necessary.
(Feedback is a must while monitoring.)
- Hey.
- What are you going to write?
I need to grab my note.
(The compliment boosts his enthusiasm.)
Where's my bag?
(The product photo shoot begins at 2pm.)
Wonderful.
(She's not frozen anymore.)
Very good.
I love it.
(A sudden change)
Be bold.
(The veteran of 24 years returns.)
Perfect.
Incredible.
It's perfect.
(Off to a successful start)
(Seo Jin is finally relieved.)
(The chocolate mushroom brings his note for feedback.)
(Here's a note for you.)
You write it down.
Aren't you going to write it?
You write better than I do.
(And My Star asked Kwang Kyu.)
You think so?
I liked it when you looked down.
(Are you writing it down?)
(Staring)
Why do you keep staring at me?
- Hey.
- What?
- But you're good at this.
- I'm not.
I don't know anything about fashion.
Besides, I've barely seen women's underwear.
(Sad confession that can't be written)
All I remember is my mom's underwear.
The sagging one.
(Another sad confession that can't be written)
You know better than I do.
Just write what could be improved.
But I don't know anything.
Something like the pant mark that should be erased.
- Something that should be removed.
- Remove...
- Write something like that.
- Yes?
You don't know anything about fashion.
- But you do.
- Write something...
that needs to be fixed.
(A big mission is given to Kwang Kyu...)
(who doesn't know anything about fashion or underwear.)
Okay. Here we go.
(In the meantime, My Star is working hard.)
I don't look that pretty...
- on the side.
- What was that?
I don't look pretty from the side.
Then let's look forward...
- Okay.
- if you're okay with that.
I guess she looks better from the left side.
She likes to show her left side.
- It's the same for most people.
- What?
- Really?
- Yes.
But it's the right side for me.
Do you have a preferred side?
(Do you have a preferred side?)
(Teasing his older bestie)
Is it the left side for you?
- Yes.
- Really?
But it's the right side for me.
(Firm)
(My Star takes photos from the left side.)
What about my belly?
(Her belly stirs up the studio.)
(What do we do?)
- Secretary.
- Yes?
- Do something about my belly.
- What?
My belly.
- Yes?
- Do something about my belly.
- What?
- My belly.
(What she wants to hear is that she doesn't have any belly.)
What's she saying?
(He didn't hear her.)
Your belly?
Oh, I'll keep my eye on that.
- Okay.
- Your belly...
Your belly needs to be removed.
(Goodbye, Kwang Kyu.)
You don't have to write that down.
(Just say I don't have a belly.)
(Secretary 1 who's diligent yet clueless)
(Erase her belly.)
(Typo in belly)
(Is there anything else to write?)
What about the polymastia?
(What she wants to hear is that she has no polymastia.)
(This time, it's about polymastia.)
The polymastia.
(Seo Jin, help me.)
(I'll handle it, Kwang Kyu.)
What about the polymastia?
(The correct answer is that you don't have any.)
We can photoshop it.
What?
We can always photoshop it. Don't worry.
Can you tell?
(Please say there isn't any.)
We can always photoshop it.
(Treat My Star like a 5-year-old.)
(Bombarding the 5-year-old with brutal facts)
(Dizzy)
(Writing down the polymastia)
- There's a lot of work to be done.
- What?
There's a lot to erase.
Cut.
All done.
Good job.
- Good job.
(The first outfit shoot ends on a good note.)
(Seo Jin comes forward in no time.)
(Quickly helping her put on the robe)
Did you monitor it?
- Did you write the feedback?
- He's writing it.
My secretary is writing it down.
Really? Right.
Kwang Kyu wrote it?
(It's this way.)
Go this way.
Excuse me.
(Escorting My Star himself)
(My Star checks the monitor.)
My thighs are so thick.
No, they're great.
What about the polymastia?
Enough with the polymastia.
(The secretary can only take this much.)
Do you know what the polymastia is?
The polymastia?
Poly...
Looking puffy?
(Looking puffy?)
I don't know what that is. What's that?
Do you think Seo Jin knows?
I bet he does.
It's the women's language.
He'd know.
(Does Seo Jin know?)
What's different between polymastia and breast?
(What's different between polymastia and breast?)
(Are they different?)
Aren't they all part of the breast?
Hey. The polymastia is...
(Here's the answer.)
(The armpit fat)
(My Star is putting on the next outfit.)
(Staring)
Doesn't the wig make you itchy?
- What?
- Isn't it itchy?
It is itchy.
(Pitying)
I'm taking it off.
It's too tight.
(The honourable mark)
- Secretary.
- Yes?
I was too busy...
to iron her outfit.
Can you help me?
- You want me to iron it?
- Yes.
- How?
- I ironed everything else.
Okay.
I didn't have time to iron this T-shirt.
I'll do it.
It shouldn't be wrinkled.
Okay.
Do I use this?
- Yes, here's the steamer.
- Okay.
Do you know how to use it?
I've seen it on home shopping.
I've always wanted to try it. This is actually great.
(Curious)
- Do I hold it?
- Yes.
(Rubbing carefully)
(Looking like a laundromat guy)
Do you iron at home?
Sometimes.
Not much these days, but I used to do it a lot in the past.
You don't?
Hot.
It's hot.
(Hot)
Gosh, that's hot.
I knew the dog was barking this morning for a reason.
(Why does this always happen to Kwang Kyu?)
Now, it's the iron.
(Be careful with the iron.)
(I'm getting a bad feeling about this.)
(Thud)
It didn't break.
(His older bestie is clumsy.)
It slipped.
(It slipped.)
(Staring)
(I'll do it.)
How do you do it?
Just keep going.
(With one hand behind his back)
It works well.
Yes.
(Unfortunately, it's not a product placement.)
(The Young Master from New York enjoys ironing.)
- Was that your first time ironing?
- Oh, right.
I don't do it.
How was it?
I barely used the iron before,
and it was flat iron.
(The old man was impressed by the new iron.)
I never used that before.
Where's the memo?
Kwang Kyu, you need to brief it.
- The memo.
- The memo?
Over there.
(Time to check the feedback on her first outfit)
First,
your first outfit was black.
while monitoring, I noticed...
the wrinkles around your bellybutton need to be erased.
They're not wrinkles. They're marks.
The marks.
Erase the marks.
Second, in front of the mic...
I mean, the logo on the jacket.
Erase the logo on the jacket.
(During the shoot)
Erase the logo...
on her jacket.
There's a logo on her jacket.
(Seo Jin contributed to the second feedback.)
That shouldn't be there?
Third, as you mentioned it,
erase the belly.
We need the CGI for that.
Do we need the CGI for that?
(Do we need the CGI for that?)
(Gulping)
I'm okay with it,
- but you mentioned it.
- Okay.
(He barely passed it.)
(The first feedback was successful.)
Okay. Excuse me.
I'm going to the restroom.
I...
Don't lower your chin too much.
No? Okay.
- Keep your chin up.
- Up?
And don't look too forward.
- Okay.
- Tilt your head.
- Sideways?
- Like this.
- Okay.
- Glare at the camera.
- You know what to do.
- Okay.
Why do you keep your chin down?
- That's not good.
- Okay.
(The thinker secretary also knows how to compliment.)
You're good at photo shoots.
(Sweet life hack from the photo shoot master)
I don't look good in front.
So I always tilt my head.
If I keep my chin down, you can't really see it.
But when looking sideways, you need to tilt your head.
If you tilt your head,
you can see this side.
(Try Seo Genie's advice.)
(Waiting for My Star to get changed)
I have a runny nose.
Tissue, please.
(My Star has a runny nose.)
Thank you.
(Wiping her nose with the tissue)
Watch your nails.
(Detailed)
It'll go in your nose.
Here you are.
(Taking care of the dirty tissue)
(Groaning)
(My Star is starting to get tired.)
Let me check your nose.
(Worried)
I'm leaving.
Let me fix your lips.
No.
Give me that.
I don't want to fix my lips.
Come on. Fix it.
No.
- Fix it.
- No.
I don't want to.
I have to get changed too.
- She doesn't like it?
- In Young hates...
applying lip gloss.
She always refuses to put it on.
Then don't do it.
She has to.
For the photo shoot.
Her lips need to look moist.
No.
- Sit down.
- No.
Then you do it for me.
- I can't do that.
- You're my secretary.
(Treat her like a 5-year-old boy.)
Do it for me.
- Put the lip gloss on me.
- You want me to do it?
The other way.
(Genie will even babysit.)
(Yet he's careful.)
I think you're erasing it.
(Kwang Kyu watches them closely.)
(Wait a minute.)
We're not ready for the shoot yet.
They seem to have a lot in common...
for being mean.
(For being mean)
They keep muttering.
They go, "I'm not doing it. I don't want to do it."
(My Star hates applying anything on her lips.)
(And neither does Seo Jin.)
(My Star hates waiting.)
(Seo Jin doesn't know what it means to wait.)
They both have...
the same dimples.
As if they were siblings,
they both have dimples.
I think they have a lot in common.
(They have the same dimples as if they were siblings.)
Let's get to it!
- Okay.
- Are you ready?
Let's do this.
Here comes the princess!
- Hi.
(The princess is happy about the shout-out.)
Our dear princess. How pretty.
(5-year-old mode off, work mode on)
Can you look down a little?
That's it.
(Moving straight to the next outfit)
(The shoot continues for 3 hours without a break.)
Nice.
(My Star is quickly wearing out.)
She's cool.
(Staring)
You know how you get tired over time?
You lose energy, become tired, and get exhausted.
But the photos turn out great.
- It's interesting.
- That's interesting.
- Why does that happen?
- I don't know.
- Was it the case for you?
- Yes.
Photos turned out better when I was tired and drained.
(Jotting down the tip from the pictorial pro Seo Jin)
She looks less puffy now.
That's why.
You lose the puffiness and become drawn over time.
In Young looks different from the morning at the house.
(My Star's on-and-off moments are clear.)
Okay.
(Yawning)
(Kwang Kyu, who looks as tired as My Star, actually...)
Here comes the princess!
Nice!
Five minutes before the setup!
Welcome!
Here she comes!
(Kwang Kyu has overdone himself today.)
Should I drink one of these? Gosh.
Oh, dear.
Do you want one too?
My gosh. This looks good.
The packaging is neat.
(A refreshing pick-me-up has appeared.)
(Kwang Kyu opens a packet and pours it into the ice cup.)
Nice colour.
(He even prepares a cup for Seo Jin.)
- What's this?
- This right here is...
- Yes?
- a caffeine-free drink...
that people drink these days.
It's made with black hoof mushrooms.
- Is that so?
- It's a healthy drink.
(Black hoof mushroom in one packet of drink)
(I'd better try it then.)
(Drinking nonstop)
Since it's caffeine-free,
it won't stop you from falling asleep,
which is nice.
Having one every night will help me get a good night's sleep.
Look at you chug it.
You might sleep like a baby today.
Routine.
- Let's resume.
- Okay.
Here.
What's that?
It's to give you a boost.
- It's a mushroom drink.
- Black hoof mushroom.
- It's a black hoof mushroom drink.
- A mushroom drink?
I love it.
- Isn't it good?
- It is.
But where's my straw?
(You're not exactly the sharpest.)
Oh, right.
Don't frown. What's with all the frowning?
- Is frowning a must?
- Yes.
- Here.
- I need my straw.
To think I'd forget a straw.
Isn't it okay?
Yes, it's nice.
Please send it to your parents as a Chuseok gift.
Great idea.
- It's a healthy drink.
- Exactly.
Absolutely.
(It's perfect for My Star, who is sensitive to trends.)
Great work.
Here goes the princess!
(Cleared the pictorial photoshoot)
- Great work today.
- Great work.
Great work.
- It was tough, wasn't it?
- Yes.
(When tired, bring on the meat.)
Look at me. I was thoughtlessly going to eat it.
- What?
- Weren't you going all out today?
I was going to,
but Waterbomb is in a few days.
- You can start tomorrow.
- Just eat a moderate amount.
Moderate amount? I'm bad at it.
Why are you shaking?
(I've worked hard today, so let's eat.)
Marriage... How long has it been?
It's been 1 year and 6 months.
- Since you dated him?
- Yes.
Did you meet your boyfriend through a blind date?
I did.
A friend of mine told me to meet him,
but I hated the idea of it.
Blind dates weren't my thing back then.
I loved the time I spent alone.
To skip the blind date...
I was with my sister and my friend.
I told the guy, "I'm fine with the blind date if you come today."
"If not, I'm cancelling tomorrow's date."
But he came.
The thing is, guys get scared when they see me.
They can hardly meet my eyes, much like Kwang Kyu.
No way. I look you in the eyes.
My boyfriend...
met my eyes...
and smiled while saying hi.
He has a dimple just like you, Seo Jin.
I like guys who look cute when they smile.
Guys who look cute when smiling.
(He won over My Star with his bright smile.)
You must like dimples.
I want a happy married life this time.
Did you already set a date?
- We did.
- You did?
It was simply, "Let's hold it near the end of the year."
You never know until the day.
Many couples break up while preparing for marriage.
You're not jealous, are you?
No.
I believe you never know until you walk down the aisle.
My boyfriend said the same thing.
Because you seemed like a pro at dating,
I wanted to ask for advice.
You want to know what men think and such.
Ladies kind of have a thing for him, you know?
- He doesn't get it.
- For Seo Jin?
Rumours among the celebrities have it that...
once he gets you, you're a goner.
(You're a goner!)
- For real?
- Yes.
- Once he gets you, you're a goner?
(Once I get you, you're a goner.)
They say you'll cry tears of blood.
(They say you'll cry tears of blood.)
It's not just regular tears, but tears of blood.
- What?
- Really?
You've got to be careful not to get dumped.
I was like, "Is Lee Seo Jin like that?"
That's how I reacted.
She and I had drinks together once.
- She cried because of him.
- Really?
- That lady?
- Yes.
I didn't know who she was crying because of.
- I asked what was going on.
- Right.
It was him.
(It was because of him!)
He's a baddie.
I'm the one who cries.
I'm guessing you treat women really well.
That's the problem.
For real? It's the problem?
He's only nice for three days.
- Three months.
- For real?
Three months in, I slowly want some alone time...
- You find it a hassle.
- and don't want to meet every day.
It's a burden.
I slowly return to myself.
Your personal life must be important to you.
- Seo Jin.
- Correct.
Why do you lose steam?
Does love last that long?
It should last long.
- But...
- I have no right to say it,
- since I'm divorced.
- Exactly.
I want us to last long.
I do, but it doesn't work out.
- Right. There are guys like that.
- Exactly.
I'm not to blame. Love is.
(I'm not to blame. Love is.)
(Laughing)
You're a real baddie.
(Saying lines of a baddie)
He's a baddie.
(A sinful man using love as an excuse)
I'm getting scared.
Of what?
- I'm the loyal type.
- Right.
That's how a relationship lasts long.
Right?
My first marriage didn't work out,
but I have a boyfriend now.
- What if he loses steam?
- Who?
My boyfriend. Or even me.
The relationship can last if your partner keeps it going,
even if you lose steam.
- Is that so?
- Yes.
But when the guy changes...
I don't give him a second chance.
That's going to cut the relationship short.
Why must I date someone who has no feelings for me?
I'm guessing you've never cried over men before.
- Me?
- Yes.
No, I cry a ton after turning around.
I cry a ton, but in front of the guy,
- "Fine. Whatever."
- I see.
But after I turn around...
(Deep down, My Star has a soft heart.)
Hurry up.
Tell me a tip on how to maintain the heart-fluttering feeling.
Come on.
I'd have married had I had one.
I'd have dated for long had I had one.
Really. Tell me.
I'm still a baby compared to you two.
What baby? You've already had the experience.
I have the most experience out of here.
We were married for six months.
We had separate rooms. But guess what?
I don't regret it. Why?
Because I had the experience.
- But you didn't.
- True.
What were you doing in the meantime?
- I agree.
- Right?
Don't you think it's about time for Kwang Kyu to get married?
The standard he has for women is very high.
- Is that so?
- Yes.
Kwang Kyu, what's your ideal type?
(Startled)
Ten years ago, she had to be 165cm tall.
- She had to have thin ankles.
- Okay.
- She had to have thick hair.
- She had to have straight hair.
- Okay.
- She had to have pretty hands.
- You sure were picky.
No. That was me ten years ago.
You were really picky even ten years ago.
- True.
- Ten years ago, you were fifty.
Fine. Yes, that was my ideal type.
- In Young...
- There's nothing wrong with it.
- It's okay.
- I only have one condition now.
- You've given up.
- Of course.
I just wish she had thicker hair.
You wish she had thicker hair?
(Looking for a lady who will fill up his baldness)
To be frank, I think you need to date...
for two years before marriage.
I'm still single because the relationships...
didn't last for two years.
- Women...
- Yes?
feel great happiness when they date men who really love them.
Of course.
- Keep a relationship for a while.
- Okay.
My mom passed away...
four years ago.
That's when I thought about...
how great it'd be to have a husband.
Two daughters...
- Your family has two girls?
- took care of everything.
So...
My mom suddenly passed away from a myocardial infarction.
My mom... When the hospital...
handed my mom's body to me,
I had no idea what to do.
Had I had a husband, how much would things have changed?
I got married after having that thought.
(The sudden loss made her realise the need to marry.)
If I got married,
I'd feel reassured.
Our family has no sons.
(Married to rely on someone)
- That's why I got married.
- You shouldn't get married...
for such a reason.
True, it was wrong of me.
Either way,
there's a need to be more cautious about the second marriage.
Have you had such an experience?
You fight, right?
As we've been together for over a year, we're getting into fights.
Here's what happened.
Listen, okay?
I like cooking for others.
I made us a meal...
and asked when he'd get home.
I don't bother him during work.
But wanting him...
to have a warm dinner, I only call him then...
to ask when he'll be back.
- Nice.
- But...
that puts a burden on him.
He said, "I feel like I must have dinner at the time you set."
"It's too stifling."
He's already lost steam.
Totally.
He has totally lost steam.
For real?
I'm sure he wasn't like that at first.
- He wasn't.
- Right?
At first, he would've come whenever you called.
He still comes.
But he brought that up during our fight.
Exactly, so he's always had that in mind.
When you're in love,
you don't say it even if you feel like it.
- That's true.
- Right?
(You're actually right.)
What do I do?
(What do I do?)
Overcome with joint prayers or something.
What prayer?
What joint prayer?
(Prayers for turning over new love)
- Right.
- Well,
do an early morning prayer or something.
Or break up with him.
- Okay?
- Gosh.
(Morning prayers or breaking up?)
I'm grateful that he hasn't been married before.
I feel bad about it too.
These two aren't good at giving advice.
They can't date women.
(These singles are useless.)
I'm the winner for dating someone.
I've never taken a break.
I've never once taken a break from dating.
- I...
- Here comes the dating princess.
(She solved her dating problems herself.)
How were you in the past to say that...
you've turned over a new leaf?
There was a huge scandal.
- What? For cussing at your manager?
- Yes.
- Unconsciously, I...
- But...
We were close, but I still cussed at him.
But here's the thing.
They said I went on a power trip.
Like, I only ride first class.
The articles said that...
I didn't go on flights if it wasn't first class.
("Seo Cussed at Staff, Demands Schedule Change and First Class")
But I wasn't like that.
- Who said that?
- I'm not being humble,
but I know my place.
Everything turned into me going on a power trip and such.
But the reason I'm turning over a new leaf is...
Rather than denying it,
accepting everything...
and accepting the fact that I was shameless in the past...
is part...
of the process of becoming...
more successful.
With that, wouldn't I become a better person?
That was what crossed my mind.
"Looking them up and down."
I was in the wrong.
(Seo In Young admits to her past mistakes in her style.)
When I get tired, I lie down and watch TV.
(My Star frankly showed off her true self.)
(Breathing heavily)
(Do you believe in salvation?)
(Yes!)
(Turning over a new leaf and making a fresh start)
Here's what changed the most about me.
My dad tried to get me admitted to the hospital...
because of too much shopping.
He even looked up some places.
You must've bought a lot of shoes.
I had a gigantic collection.
You were addicted to shoes.
I had several hundred pairs of shoes.
- You were a shoe addict.
- I was.
Several hundred pairs of shoes?
Hundreds...
She's the first to have popularized the word "new arrival."
- That's right.
- Our talk earlier...
- Right.
- reminded me of it.
(Original "new arrival" Seo In Young)
(She showed off her absolute love for shoes.)
(My Star captivated the public with her trendy style.)
I no longer have worldly desires.
You still have that many shoes despite not having worldly desires?
Those are all cheap shoes...
and ones I already had.
I don't buy new ones now.
(Innocent)
But I do have dilemmas.
Can I carry this bag when I'm turning over a new leaf?
- I have two left.
- Right.
Can I wear this when I'm turning over a new leaf?
Can I buy this?
I'm turning over a new leaf.
That's what happens.
It's not turning over a new leaf, but...
Turning over a new leaf is reforming me.
Yes, turning over a new leaf...
- It's reshaping me.
- Reshaping you.
I now have a goal.
Turn over a new leaf.
In short,
not buying things...
will help me cure...
this disease.
(A self-driven change toward a new beginning)
But you had your struggles before turning over a new leaf.
- Yes.
- Your worldly desires stopped...
before that, right?
No. Back then, I still had it.
- Before turning over a new leaf?
- I did, but I sold everything.
I had to stop having worldly desires.
Since I wasn't active,
I couldn't make a living...
without letting go of my worldly desires...
- Could you not live?
- and selling things.
Your life had hit rock bottom.
It did. For real.
(As the gap grew longer, reality proved tough.)
I see.
What was the use of...
carrying designer bags and buying...
all the new arrivals?
- Aren't I right?
- Yes.
What was the use of a nice car?
(My Star found clarity through letting go.)
I like this comfortable life.
Nice.
That's what I think.
Here's what I want to do.
While turning over a new leaf,
when I sing or go on a shoot,
I want to be bright from start to finish.
It's not just us...
- who have it tough.
- True.
Let's make it less obvious.
- Keep a poker face.
- Like this.
- You can't hide your feelings.
- No.
- Smile, Seo Jin.
- Yes, smile.
Smile. He and I really get along well.
(We get along well.)
What score would you give her?
She doesn't have to turn over a new leaf.
I don't think it's bad at all.
She's putting in all the effort and trying hard.
(My Star through Seo Jin's eyes)
In Young is very discreet and has good manners.
She has her reasons. She's not thoughtless.
(My Star is more than meets the eye.)
She never crosses the line.
(What was the best care today?)
The best was...
when Kwang Kyu wrote things down.
I thought he'd stop after a few times.
But he kept writing until the very end.
As for Seo Jin, him simply being next to me...
He pays great attention.
He acts cold, but secretly cares,
like brushing dirt off your face.
Seo Jin was like a real big brother.
I love it when men are like that.
It's adorable.
Doesn't it make your heart flutter?
He had a way of dealing with women.
(Is that so?)
My Star.
There's dirt on you.
(Let me get it for you.)
My Star.
(Seo In Young is turning over a new leaf.)
(The production press conference of "The Scandal")
(Among the dazzling celebrities,)
(who is today's My Star?)
(My Star candidate 1, Nana)
It's been a while, Nana.
Do you need honey?
- Honey?
- I'm okay.
(My Star candidate 2, Son Ye Jin)
- A film camera.
- It's a film camera.
(Among the ladies making the secretaries' hearts flutter)
(Today's real My Star, Ji Chang Wook)
(Chang Wook was in last season as My Star.)
Was there anything...
that I did as I wanted?
(He was greatly bullied by the secretaries.)
(Genie will do everything as My Star wants this time.)
What?
(Fully charged with dopamine)
(My Star's getaway care)
I haven't felt this in a while.
You know, getting tired while hanging out.
People can't live by only doing things they like.
(Life never goes as planned.)
(How will the first-ever aftercare go?)
(My Genie Secretary)